innovis.com 2017-04-08

# Privacy

## Last Updated: June 30, 2015

## Scope of this Policy

Innovis Data Solutions, Inc. (Innovis) has created this privacy policy in order to describe how we collect, use, maintain, share and protect your personal information when you use our website, www.innovis.com (hereinafter “Website” or “Site”) in connection with our consumer data solutions and services, including identity verification, fraud prevention, receivables management and credit information. 

This privacy policy applies to information collected when you visit our Website. It does not apply to information collected in any other way, including information collected offline. 

## Children's Privacy

Our Website is not directed at children under the age of 13. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a minor and want to request the minor’s Innovis Credit Report, please visit our Learning Center to learn more. 

## Changes to this Policy

We may revise this privacy policy from time to time. If we make material changes, we will notify you by posting a notice on our Website. 

## Information Collection on our Website

Innovis strives to limit its collection of personal information to that necessary for the promotion, offering and administration of our services. Our Site collects the following types of information when you visit: 

  * Personally identifiable information (PII); and,
  * Non-personally identifiable information.

## Personally Identifiable Information

Based on the nature of your transaction with us, you may provide to us certain PII such as name, company name, job function, email, physical address, or telephone number. In addition, if you are creating an Innovis Personal Account, submitting a Fraud & Activity Duty Alert or a Security Freeze request through our Site, you will be required to provide your date of birth and Social Security Number in order for us to process your request. 

If you order your Innovis Credit Report you can create a personal account which will allow you to initiate a dispute on your report if you believe information contained therein is incomplete or inaccurate. By doing so, when you log in, you have the option of providing us with additional information during the online dispute which may be of a personal nature. The additional information you provide to us is within your discretion. 

## Non-personally Identifiable Information

When you visit our Website, we may collect and store general Internet data, including your internet protocol (IP) address, domain name, browser type, date and time of access, which of our web pages you visited, the referring Uniform Resource Locator (URL) and how long you spend on each page. This information may be collected to assist us in making improvements to our Website or to administer our Website. We do not link this information to any PII. Innovis may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate these services (e.g., maintenance, analysis, audit, development). These third parties have limited access to your information and only to perform these tasks on our behalf. 

## Information Use

The information collected through our Site may be used: 

  * To process online consumer requests, including updating your Innovis Credit Report which in turn updates our consumer reporting database; 
  * To respond to your inquiries or otherwise correspond with you if, for instance, you are contacting our customer support service or requesting product information;
  * To maintain your account;
  * For purposes permitted by your organization's agreement(s) with us (if any) for the provision of products and services;
  * To maintain the security and integrity of our Website, products and services; and
  * For the administration, review and/or the improvement of the content of our Website, products or services.

## Cookies

We use cookies to collect Website usage data, to improve the Site and our services, as well as your experience with the Site. Cookies are pieces of information generated by a web server and stored in your computer, ready for future access. The information can then be used to identify you when you return to the Site, to personalize web content, and in some cases suggest items of potential interest based on previous use. Innovis may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. You can control cookies through your browser settings and other tools. 

## Third-Party Links and Websites

This policy applies to Innovis’ Website. However, you are able to access third-party sites through our Site by, for example, clicking on hyperlinks to those third-party sites from within our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of any third-party sites, and if you visit those websites, we encourage you to review their respective privacy policies. 

Third party links on our Site are provided for your convenience and to provide further information or serve as a resource. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). Innovis exercises no control whatsoever over such other websites and web-based resources and is not responsible or liable for the availability thereof or the content, advertising, products or other materials thereon. Innovis shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss incurred or suffered by any user in connection therewith. Your access and use of linked websites, including information, material, products and services therein, is solely at your own risk. 

## Choice, Opt-Out and Online Tracking

As a user of our Website you make the decision whether to proceed with activities that request PII, such as requesting follow-up contact regarding our services and products, or to create an account, initiate an alert, security freeze or dispute. Note however that if you do not provide the requested information you may not be able to complete certain online transactions or benefit from certain services. 

If you do not wish to continue receiving emails or other communications from Innovis, you can also notify us by email, phone or by contacting us in writing at the address listed in the Point of Contact section. 

Innovis does not track consumers’ online activities over time and across third party websites or online services. However, other third parties may be conducting online tracking on our Site. To learn more about the choices you have regarding online tracking, please visit these sites: 

<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>   
<http://www.youradchoices.com/>

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We may disclose information we collect through this Site to third parties in order to complete a transaction that you requested, as permitted by your organization's customer agreement(s) (if any) with us, or as permitted by law. 

When you initiate a dispute resolution regarding your Innovis Credit Report, we may disclose the information you provide to the entity that provided the disputed data. We also provide your information to businesses that have a permissible purpose pursuant to the Fair Credit Reporting Act, or a permitted use under Title V of the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act. 

Innovis may also disclose your information for the following reasons: 

  * When required by law, subpoena or other legal process, when pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings;
  * When necessary to investigate, take action or prevent suspected or actual illegal activities, fraud, or potential threats to safety or personal physical safety; and,
  * If our company or our assets are acquired or purchased by another company, that company will assume responsibility for the personal information collected by us through our Website and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding the information collected through our Website, as described in this privacy policy.

## Access and Correction of Personal Information and Closing Your Account

You may access and update personal information you have provided through our Website, or, request that we close your personal account by contacting Innovis Consumer Assistance at the address or telephone number listed below. If you wish to receive a copy of your Innovis Credit Report, please contact Innovis Consumer Assistance at the address or telephone number listed below. 

Innovis  
Attn: Consumer Assistance  
P.O. Box 1640  
Pittsburgh, PA 15230  
Phone: 1-800-540-2505  
Fax: 1-877-314-0117  

## Retention of Information

Innovis retains personal information in its consumer reporting database for such time as allowed by law. Also, Innovis retains personal information while you are a customer and your account is in existence, or as needed, to provide you services or product information. We may retain your personal information even after you have closed your account to comply with our contractual, statutory or other legal obligations. 

## Security and Confidentiality

Innovis strives to protect personal information that we collect, maintain and disclose through the use of reasonable administrative, physical and technical safeguards. Our products and/or services online are transmitted through a secure sockets layer (SSL) transmission, which is a protocol for establishing a secure connection for transmission of your personal information. Our security program is designed to: (1) ensure the security and confidentiality of personal information, (2) protect against any anticipated threats or hazards to the security or integrity of the information, and (3) protect against unauthorized access, alteration and unlawful disclosure of the information. 

In the course of business, Innovis may collect or ask that you disclose your Social Security Number. To the extent practicable, Innovis protects the confidentiality of all information we collect, including Social Security Numbers. Accordingly, we prohibit the unlawful disclosure of personal information, including Social Security Numbers, and limit access to same. We dispose of such information by taking reasonable measures to protect against unauthorized access to or use of the information. 

## Point of Contact

If you have any questions or comments about Innovis’ privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at: 

Innovis  
Attn: Chief Compliance Officer  
P.O. Box 163250  
Columbus, OH 43215  
Phone: 1-855-202-0113  
Fax: 1-866-291-7413
